[{"version_UUID": "3d10d834-6620-4dbe-ae23-088b52bd33f7", "creation_time": "2022-01-01T03:00:38.024522Z", "creation_date": "2022-01-01", "creation_day_since_launch": 2759, "creation_year": 2022, "creation_month": 1, "site_cat": 5, "type": "adult", "lon": 89.5592484, "lat": 25.2854259, "movelab_annotation": null, "movelab_annotation_euro": null, "tiger_responses": {}, "tiger_responses_text": {"question_6": "question_6_answer_62", "question_13": "question_13_answer_132"}, "site_responses": null, "site_responses_text": null, "tigaprob_cat": 0, "visible": true, "latest_version": true, "n_photos": 0, "final_expert_status_text": 1, "responses": [{"id": 278339, "translated_question": "What type of mosquito do you think it was?", "translated_answer": "Common mosquito", "question_id": 6, "question": "question_6", "answer_id": 62, "answer": "question_6_answer_62", "answer_value": null, "report": "3d10d834-6620-4dbe-ae23-088b52bd33f7"}, {"id": 278340, "translated_question": "Where did you find the mosquito?", "translated_answer": "In a building", "question_id": 13, "question": "question_13", "answer_id": 132, "answer": "question_13_answer_132", "answer_value": null, "report": "3d10d834-6620-4dbe-ae23-088b52bd33f7"}], "cached_visible": null, "point": "SRID=4326;POINT (89.5592484 25.2854259)", "nuts_3": null, "nuts_2": null, "country": null, "session": null}, {"version_UUID": "6824f5fd-5659-4233-bfe1-b30020ee3a10", "creation_time": "2022-01-01T01:02:16.759603Z", "creation_date": "2022-01-01", "creation_day_since_launch": 2759, "creation_year": 2022, "creation_month": 1, "site_cat": 5, "type": "adult", "lon": 58.1095534, "lat": 23.673047, "movelab_annotation": null, "movelab_annotation_euro": null, "tiger_responses": {}, "tiger_responses_text": {"question_6": "question_6_answer_62", "question_13": "question_13_answer_132"}, "site_responses": null, "site_responses_text": null, "tigaprob_cat": 0, "visible": true, "latest_version": true, "n_photos": 0, "final_expert_status_text": 1, "responses": [{"id": 278341, "translated_question": "What type of mosquito do you think it was?", "translated_answer": "Common mosquito", "question_id": 6, "question": "question_6", "answer_id": 62, "answer": "question_6_answer_62", "answer_value": null, "report": "6824f5fd-5659-4233-bfe1-b30020ee3a10"}, {"id": 278342, "translated_question": "Where did you find the mosquito?", "translated_answer": "In a building", "question_id": 13, "question": "question_13", "answer_id": 132, "answer": "question_13_answer_132", "answer_value": null, "report": "6824f5fd-5659-4233-bfe1-b30020ee3a10"}], "cached_visible": null, "point": "SRID=4326;POINT (58.1095534 23.673047)", "nuts_3": null, "nuts_2": null, "country": null, "session": null}, {"version_UUID": "9c99ac4c-7d47-4352-8288-e58628275259", "creation_time": "2022-01-01T01:08:11.169936Z", "creation_date": "2022-01-01", "creation_day_since_launch": 2759, "creation_year": 2022, "creation_month": 1, "site_cat": 5, "type": "adult", "lon": 58.1095532, "lat": 23.673048, "movelab_annotation": null, "movelab_annotation_euro": null, "tiger_responses": {}, "tiger_responses_text": {"question_6": "question_6_answer_64", "question_13": "question_13_answer_132"}, "site_responses": null, "site_responses_text": null, "tigaprob_cat": 0, "visible": true, "latest_version": true, "n_photos": 0, "final_expert_status_text": 1, "responses": [{"id": 278343, "translated_question": "What type of mosquito do you think it was?", "translated_answer": "I don't know", "question_id": 6, "question": "question_6", "answer_id": 64, "answer": "question_6_answer_64", "answer_value": null, "report": "9c99ac4c-7d47-4352-8288-e58628275259"}, {"id": 278344, "translated_question": "Where did you find the mosquito?", "translated_answer": "In a building", "question_id": 13, "question": "question_13", "answer_id": 132, "answer": "question_13_answer_132", "answer_value": null, "report": "9c99ac4c-7d47-4352-8288-e58628275259"}], "cached_visible": null, "point": "SRID=4326;POINT (58.1095532 23.673048)", "nuts_3": null, "nuts_2": null, "country": null, "session": null}, {"version_UUID": "5b1b9116-e55b-4776-9162-b0af2e01bc57", "creation_time": "2022-01-01T01:29:28.286666Z", "creation_date": "2022-01-01", "creation_day_since_launch": 2759, "creation_year": 2022, "creation_month": 1, "site_cat": 5, "type": "bite", "lon": 3.1008, "lat": 36.7323291, "movelab_annotation": null, "movelab_annotation_euro": null, "tiger_responses": null, "tiger_responses_text": null, "site_responses": null, "site_responses_text": null, "tigaprob_cat": 0, "visible": true, "latest_version": true, "n_photos": 0, "final_expert_status_text": 1, "responses": [{"id": 278347, "translated_question": "How many bites do you have and where are they on your body?", "translated_answer": "", "question_id": 1, "question": "question_1", "answer_id": 11, "answer": "N/A", "answer_value": "5", "report": "5b1b9116-e55b-4776-9162-b0af2e01bc57"}, {"id": 278348, "translated_question": "When were you bitten?", "translated_answer": "In the last 24 hours", "question_id": 5, "question": "question_5", "answer_id": 52, "answer": "question_5_answer_52", "answer_value": null, "report": "5b1b9116-e55b-4776-9162-b0af2e01bc57"}, {"id": 278349, "translated_question": "What time was it?", "translated_answer": "Night", "question_id": 3, "question": "question_3", "answer_id": 34, "answer": "question_3_answer_34", "answer_value": null, "report": "5b1b9116-e55b-4776-9162-b0af2e01bc57"}, {"id": 278350, "translated_question": "Where did they bite you?", "translated_answer": "Inside a vehicle?", "question_id": 4, "question": "question_4", "answer_id": 41, "answer": "question_4_answer_41", "answer_value": null, "report": "5b1b9116-e55b-4776-9162-b0af2e01bc57"}, {"id": 278351, "translated_question": "Where did they bite you?", "translated_answer": "Head", "question_id": 2, "question": "question_2", "answer_id": 21, "answer": "question_2_answer_21", "answer_value": "1", "report": "5b1b9116-e55b-4776-9162-b0af2e01bc57"}, {"id": 278352, "translated_question": "Where did they bite you?", "translated_answer": "Right arm", "question_id": 2, "question": "question_2", "answer_id": 23, "answer": "question_2_answer_23", "answer_value": "1", "report": "5b1b9116-e55b-4776-9162-b0af2e01bc57"}, {"id": 278353, "translated_question": "Where did they bite you?", "translated_answer": "Left arm", "question_id": 2, "question": "question_2", "answer_id": 22, "answer": "question_2_answer_22", "answer_value": "1", "report": "5b1b9116-e55b-4776-9162-b0af2e01bc57"}, {"id": 278354, "translated_question": "Where did they bite you?", "translated_answer": "Left leg", "question_id": 2, "question": "question_2", "answer_id": 25, "answer": "question_2_answer_25", "answer_value": "1", "report": "5b1b9116-e55b-4776-9162-b0af2e01bc57"}, {"id": 278355, "translated_question": "Where did they bite you?", "translated_answer": "Right leg", "question_id": 2, "question": "question_2", "answer_id": 26, "answer": "question_2_answer_26", "answer_value": "1", "report": "5b1b9116-e55b-4776-9162-b0af2e01bc57"}], "cached_visible": null, "point": "SRID=4326;POINT (3.1008 36.7323291)", "nuts_3": null, "nuts_2": null, "country": null, "session": null}, {"version_UUID": "305b06c1-b1ad-45b9-8b0e-d97d5f5b1b61", "creation_time": "2022-01-01T04:18:39.086893Z", "creation_date": "2022-01-01", "creation_day_since_launch": 2759, "creation_year": 2022, "creation_month": 1, "site_cat": 5, "type": "adult", "lon": 56.295932, "lat": 27.1868558, "movelab_annotation": null, "movelab_annotation_euro": null, "tiger_responses": {}, "tiger_responses_text": {"question_6": "question_6_answer_61", "question_7": "question_7_answer_724", "question_13": "question_13_answer_132"}, "site_responses": null, "site_responses_text": null, "tigaprob_cat": 0, "visible": true, "latest_version": true, "n_photos": 0, "final_expert_status_text": 1, "responses": [{"id": 278356, "translated_question": "What type of mosquito do you think it was?", "translated_answer": "Invasive Aedes", "question_id": 6, "question": "question_6", "answer_id": 61, "answer": "question_6_answer_61", "answer_value": null, "report": "305b06c1-b1ad-45b9-8b0e-d97d5f5b1b61"}, {"id": 278357, "translated_question": "What does the mosquito look like?", "translated_answer": "Thorax 4", "question_id": 7, "question": "question_7", "answer_id": 714, "answer": "question_7_answer_714", "answer_value": null, "report": "305b06c1-b1ad-45b9-8b0e-d97d5f5b1b61"}, {"id": 278358, "translated_question": "What does the mosquito look like?", "translated_answer": "Abdomen 4", "question_id": 7, "question": "question_7", "answer_id": 724, "answer": "question_7_answer_724", "answer_value": null, "report": "305b06c1-b1ad-45b9-8b0e-d97d5f5b1b61"}, {"id": 278359, "translated_question": "Where did you find the mosquito?", "translated_answer": "In a building", "question_id": 13, "question": "question_13", "answer_id": 132, "answer": "question_13_answer_132", "answer_value": null, "report": "305b06c1-b1ad-45b9-8b0e-d97d5f5b1b61"}], "cached_visible": null, "point": "SRID=4326;POINT (56.295932 27.1868558)", "nuts_3": null, "nuts_2": null, "country": null, "session": null}, {"version_UUID": "27a25149-67c9-4d64-8317-0af395038134", "creation_time": "2022-01-01T04:19:32.841631Z", "creation_date": "2022-01-01", "creation_day_since_launch": 2759, "creation_year": 2022, "creation_month": 1, "site_cat": 5, "type": "bite", "lon": 56.295932, "lat": 27.1868558, "movelab_annotation": null, "movelab_annotation_euro": null, "tiger_responses": null, "tiger_responses_text": null, "site_responses": null, "site_responses_text": null, "tigaprob_cat": 0, "visible": true, "latest_version": true, "n_photos": 0, "final_expert_status_text": 1, "responses": [{"id": 278360, "translated_question": "How many bites do you have and where are they on your body?", "translated_answer": "", "question_id": 1, "question": "question_1", "answer_id": 11, "answer": "N/A", "answer_value": "3", "report": "27a25149-67c9-4d64-8317-0af395038134"}, {"id": 278361, "translated_question": "When were you bitten?", "translated_answer": "In the last 24 hours", "question_id": 5, "question": "question_5", "answer_id": 52, "answer": "question_5_answer_52", "answer_value": null, "report": "27a25149-67c9-4d64-8317-0af395038134"}, {"id": 278362, "translated_question": "What time was it?", "translated_answer": "Night", "question_id": 3, "question": "question_3", "answer_id": 34, "answer": "question_3_answer_34", "answer_value": null, "report": "27a25149-67c9-4d64-8317-0af395038134"}, {"id": 278363, "translated_question": "Where did they bite you?", "translated_answer": "I don't know", "question_id": 4, "question": "question_4", "answer_id": 44, "answer": "question_4_answer_44", "answer_value": null, "report": "27a25149-67c9-4d64-8317-0af395038134"}, {"id": 278364, "translated_question": "Where did they bite you?", "translated_answer": "Left arm", "question_id": 2, "question": "question_2", "answer_id": 22, "answer": "question_2_answer_22", "answer_value": "1", "report": "27a25149-67c9-4d64-8317-0af395038134"}, {"id": 278365, "translated_question": "Where did they bite you?", "translated_answer": "Head", "question_id": 2, "question": "question_2", "answer_id": 21, "answer": "question_2_answer_21", "answer_value": "1", "report": "27a25149-67c9-4d64-8317-0af395038134"}, {"id": 278366, "translated_question": "Where did they bite you?", "translated_answer": "Left leg", "question_id": 2, "question": "question_2", "answer_id": 25, "answer": "question_2_answer_25", "answer_value": "1", "report": "27a25149-67c9-4d64-8317-0af395038134"}], "cached_visible": null, "point": "SRID=4326;POINT (56.295932 27.1868558)", "nuts_3": null, "nuts_2": null, "country": null, "session": null}]